傲骨之战
第一季 第三集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译      Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  吃冰棒  ABCpril
翻译      dzysteven  kahiko_情迷偽優  一点都不酷喵  胡说大王
校对      free维塔  某羽
时间轴      Avis
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free维塔
最新海外影视剧下载
你好  贾克斯叔叔
Hi, Uncle Jax.
玛娅
Maia.
你最近过得怎么样
How are you these days?
很好  好极了
Good. Very good.
看你活得这么滋润我就放心了  妈
Glad things are going so well for you, Mom.
不  玛娅  玛娅
No, M-Maia, Maia.
玛娅
Maia. M...
玛娅  亲爱的
Maia, darling.
事情不是你想的那样
That is not what it looked like.
告诉我事情是怎么样的  妈
Tell me what it looked like, Mom.
我爸被人陷害而锒铛入狱
Because my dad is in jail for something he didn't do
你却在和害他坐牢的人乱搞
and you're fucking the man who put him there?!
不许你这么跟我说话
Don't you use that language with me!
-我是想劝劝他  -真的吗
- I'm trying to talk some sense into him. - Oh, really?
怎么个劝法让他把衬衫都脱了
See, what kind of sense requires him to take off his shirt?
你觉得呢
What kind do you think?
我的天  你认真的吗
Oh, my God. Seriously?
你想说你是为了爸才这么做的吗
You're telling me you're doing this for Dad?
好  我知道了
Okay, good to know.
别
Don't...
别告诉你爸  拜托了
don't tell-tell Dad, please.
他会痛不欲生的
It will kill him.
我的天
Oh, my God.
好  完事了
Okay, it is done.
我们把一块金属取出来了
We've removed one piece of metal.
好像是榴弹碎片
Looks like shrapnel.
好  一切进展顺利  有多大
Good, it's all good. How big is it?
长三厘米  宽一厘米
Three centimeters by one.
你做得很好  尤瑟夫
You're doing fine, Yusuf.
-你能把摄像头移近些吗  -收到
- Can you move the camera closer? - Roger.
你能让牙医
Can you ask the dentist
把伤口缝合起来吗
to suture it up and close the hole?
缝几针就好
A couple of bites should do it.
只是来回穿引而已
Just tie and repeat.
很好  榴弹碎片取出来了
Good. The shrapnel's gone.
你们需要持续关注
You'll need to keep track
血压和急性发热
of the blood pressure and the fever spikes.
港湾医院
来处理次要伤口  朝你身体方向缝合
Okay, for the second lesion, sew towards yourself
注意缝合的张力
and keep tension on the stitch.
你那边还好吗  尤瑟夫
Is everything all right there, Yusuf?
这是叙利亚  医生  当然不好
It's Syria, Doctor. Clearly no.
我们好像听到有响动  轰隆隆的声音
We thought we heard a sound, a rumble.
这里一切都好
All good here.
就是看着牙医在拯救生命
Just watching a dentist save a life.
听着好像是你那边的声音  医生
Sounds like it's where you are, Doctor.
考虑到你们芝加哥的谋杀率  我很担心
With your Chicago murder rate, I'm worried.
密切关注他  我们可不想出现什么大差错
Keep monitoring him. We don't want any big changes.
我尽量晚一点再联系
I'll try to check in later,
-但我可能不在了  -兰道夫·皮科医生
- but I might be out of circulation. - Dr. Randolph Picot?
-怎么了  医生  -没错
- What is wrong, Doctor? - Yes.
-有什么事吗  -你被捕了
- What is this about? - You're under arrest.
请把你的手放到背后
Please place your hands behind your back.
我还在手术之中
I'm in the middle of an operation.
请把你的手放到背后
Please place your hands behind your back.
员工费用支出  1380万
Salaries charged as expenses: $13.8 million.
养老金固定收益所得  310万
Actuarial gain on defined benefit pensions: $3.1 million.
合伙人资金  340万
Partners capital: $3.4 million.
我们还有一位合伙人没交认购金
And we're still waiting for one capital contribution.
但按这样的预期  合伙人的
But with that anticipation, the profit for the financial year
财政年收益将达到  850万
available for division among partners: $8.5 million.
好  生意不错  恭喜大家
Good. Then we're doing great. Congrats.
有个问题
One problem.
-当然了  -文图拉网桥  那个手机塔公司
- Of course. - Ventura Bridge, the cell phone tower company.
他们的律师费还没付
They haven't paid their retainer yet.
肯定是一时疏忽
It's got to be an oversight.
可能吧  但没有他们的律师费
Well, maybe, but without their retainer,
我们少了1260万
we're down $12,600,000.
这意味着今年所有股权合伙人
That means all the equity partners will owe
都欠30多万
$300,000 more this year.
这肯定是一时疏忽  各位
It's an oversight, y'all.
文图拉网桥是个无招标合同
The Ventura Bridge is a no-bid contract going back,
合作都有五年了
what, five years?
这钱跑不掉
That's money in hand.
别担心  我打电话问一下
Don't worry. I will make a call.
最好不过了  否则我们每人30万就没了
You better, or we're all out $300,000.
戴安·洛哈特办公室
Diane Lockhart's office.
不  她在开会  我能给你转告吗
No, she's in a meeting right now, can I take a message?
好
Okay.
我能给"您"转告吗
May I take a message?
什么
What?
我能给"您"转告吗
May I take a message?
谢谢
Thanks.
"您"有什么事吗
May I help you?
你之前做过调查工作  对吗
You did a bit of investigating the other day, didn't you?
我做过调查工作吗
I did a bit of investigating?
这话每个字我都认识
I understand what those words mean,
但你得给我点语境才行
but you'll have to give me more context.
你的鞋不错
I like your shoes.
你外出拿到了集体诉讼案的人员名单
You went out and got the names for the class action.
没错  我只是  我在商场工作过
Oh, yeah. I just... I worked at the mall,
似乎和朋友随便聊聊天就能把问题解决了
and it seemed easier to just go talk to some friends.
我是这里的调查员
Hmm. I'm the investigator.
我在太岁头上动土了  是吗
Oh, I stepped on your toes, didn't I?
只此一次  下不为例
Well, it was a one-time thing.
别担心  我叫梅丽莎
Don't worry. Marissa.
我得接电话了
I have to get that.
戴安·洛哈特  我能  有什么能帮您的吗
Diane Lockhart's office. How can I... may I help you?
我知道我不该打扰你
I know. I shouldn't be interrupting you,
但皮科医生来电找你
but a Dr. Picot is on the line.
没错  他的失职案  告诉他我会回电
Yes, it's his malpractice case. Tell him I'll call him back.
不  他被逮捕了
No, no, no, he was arrested.
什么  什么时候的事
What? When?
就一小时前
Just an hour ago.
为什么
Why?
涉嫌恐怖行动
Terrorism.
我需要见我的父亲
I need to see my dad.
我是你律师
See, I'm your lawyer,
我在尽力让你免于被起诉
and I'm trying to save you from an indictment.
我还是得去见我父亲
I still need to see him.
我得警告他  我认为他被陷害了
I need to warn him. I think he's being set up.
被谁陷害了
By whom?
贾克斯叔叔和我母亲
My Uncle Jax and my mom.
好吧
Okay.
这样吧  我得去一趟
Here's the thing. I'm going.
等等  你现在就去吗
Wait, you're going now?
不  我是要和你一起去见你父亲
No, no, no. I'm going with you to visit your dad.
不  我不需要
No, I don't need...
这没得商量
That's nonnegotiable.
玛娅  你会在某个时候告诉客户说
Maia, there will be a moment when you tell a client,
"请一定照我说的做  这是为了你好"
"For your own good, you have to do what I say."
对于你来说  现在就是那样的时候
This is one of those moments for you.
所以我会允许你去探监
So, I'll allow you to visit your dad in prison,
但我要和你一起去
but I'm gonna be there.
我会听到你对他说的每一个字
I'm gonna hear everything you say to him
以及他对你说的每一个字
and everything he says to you,
这样谈话会受到律师与当事人保密协定的保护
so it's subject to attorney/client privilege.
明白了吗
Do you understand?
皮科医生吗
Oh, Dr. Picot?
我是戴安·洛哈特  你失职案的律师
I'm Diane Lockhart, your malpractice lawyer.
你惹上的麻烦不小
This is quite a situation you've gotten yourself into.
我知道  说我是恐怖分子支持者
Yes, I know, a terrorist sympathizer.
这会让我的牧师大吃一惊
Won't my rabbi be surprised.
你当时在指导位于叙利亚的开胸手术吗
And you were conducting open-heart surgery in Syria?
叙利亚一直缺乏医疗人员
Medical personnel have been so depleted in Syria
无国界医生一直在为他们提供支持
that Doctors Without Borders is providing technical support
用视频电话指导非专业人士
via Skype to nondoctors there.
我明白了  好的
I see, well, good.
这只是传讯  为了获取保释
So, this is merely an initial appearance to secure pretrial release,
所以应该不会有什么问题
so it should go fairly smoothly.
你明显没有弃保潜逃的风险
So, you're clearly not a flight risk.
我在加拿大安大略省有钓鱼度假屋
Well, I do have a fishing cabin in Ontario,
但它连厕所都要凑合着用
but it barely has a toilet.
我挺喜欢你的  医生  你很风趣
I like you, Doctor. I think you're funny,
但法庭不会喜欢这样
but the court doesn't do well with funny.
明白了  我会闭嘴的
Got it. Zip it.
你知道他是恐怖分子吗
Uh, did you know he was a terrorist?
什么
Excuse me?
你叙利亚的病人  你知道他是恐怖分子吗
Your patient in Syria, did you know he was a terrorist?
你们俩是一起的吗
Are you two together?
因为我希望她也在场  就这么简单
Because I want her there, that's all.
这还是你的案子  戴安
It's still your case, Diane.
这只是传讯
It's an initial appearance.
我不需要人手把手地帮忙
I don't need hand-holding with an initial appearance.
谁说是要帮忙了
Who said anything about hand-holding?
卢卡什么也没做
Lucca wasn't doing anything,
她有处理联邦法院案件的经验
and she has experience in federal court.
芭芭拉  我曾是全市最大的律所
Barbara, I was a name partner
的冠名合伙人
at the town's biggest firm.
没错  而我是你现在律所的冠名合伙人
Yes, and I'm a name partner at this firm.
我没有质疑你的意思
I'm not questioning that.
戴安  你还在你的律所的时候
At your firm, Diane,
你有时不也会驳回初级合伙人的意见吗
did you sometimes overrule the judgment of junior partners?
所以你是在教训我应该谦卑点儿吗
So this is a lesson in humility?
不是
No.
公诉人是科林·莫雷洛
The prosecutor is Colin Morrello.
他是最厉害的助理联邦检察官
He is their top AUSA.
所以让你们合作并不是坏主意  不是吗
It isn't wrong to have you two working together, okay?
好吧
Okay.
祝你好运
Good luck.
好吧  再见
Right. Bye.
你为什么要那么做
Why are you really doing that?
你什么意思  我想让她俩合作而已
What do you mean? I want them to work together.
不  芭芭拉  你在展示权力
Mm-mm, no, Barbara, it's a power play.
我能听出你的语气
Now, I know that sound in your voice
你别有企图的语气
when you've got some kind of hidden agenda.
她占了卢卡的办公室
She got Lucca's office.
我不想失去卢卡
I don't want to lose Lucca.
她需要感受到我们的重视
She needs to feel needed.
你看  这就是权力的问题
See, here's the problem with power.
赋予某人权力则意味着剥夺另一人的权力
You got to take it from somebody to give it to somebody else.
谢谢你  孙子
Thank you, Sun Tzu.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
对戴安友善点儿
Be nice to Diane.
别再这样管着她了  好吗
Don't rule it over her like that, huh?
我有质疑过你的领导决定吗
Do I question your leadership?
你总在质疑
All the time.
好吧
Okay.
我会照做的
I'll behave.
很好
Good.
文图拉网桥律师费的事怎么样了
Now what's going on with our Ventura Bridge retainer?
钱什么时候到位
Is it coming?
我们今天和他们的执行总裁吃午饭
Yeah, we're having lunch with the CEO today.
我们会把这事弄清楚的
We'll get to the bottom of it.
友善点儿
Be nice.
早上好  法官阁下
Good morning, Your Honor.
早安  莫雷洛先生  很高兴见到你
Good morning, Mr. Morrello. Always a pleasure.
我也感到荣幸
Likewise.
因被告有潜逃危险且危及社会
The government asks the defendant be detained pending trial,
控方请求将其还押候审
both as a flight risk and a danger to the community.
开什么玩笑  危及什么社会了
Seriously, what kind of danger to the community?!
他是没有任何犯罪前科的著名医生
He's a renowned doctor with no record.
我好像激起民愤了  法官阁下
Oh, I seem to have struck a chord over there, Your Honor.
是的  白痴总能让人上火
Yes, idiocy has a way of doing that.
好的  谢谢  有点激烈
Okay, thank you, little cordiality here.
请继续  莫雷洛先生
Continue, Mr. Morrello.
「美国法典」第18编第2339A条禁止任何人
18 U.S. Code 2339A prohibits anyone
向恐怖组织提供物质支持
from providing material support to terrorist organizations.
当皮科先生为已知恐怖分子实施手术时
When Dr. Picot operated on a known terrorist...
他并没有实施手术  法官阁下
He didn't operate, Your Honor.
他是通过视频电话辅助手术
He assisted in an operation over Skype.
不仅是辅助  他还督导手术
Not just assisted. He supervised.
他是经过训练的心脏病专家
He is a trained heart specialist,
全美只有三位  而他是其中一个
one of only three in America
可以实施那个手术的人
who could've performed that operation.
法官阁下  助理联邦检察官漏了一个关键词
Your Honor, the AUSA left one important word out of 18 U.S.C.
任何人不得"故意"向恐怖分子提供物质帮助
"No one may knowingly provide material support to a terrorist."
我们当事人不知道叙利亚的病人是谁
Our client had no idea who the patient was in Syria.
他只知道那是一个需要医疗救助的
All he knew was that he was a human being
活生生的人
in need of medical assistance.
我这有句话是皮科医生
I have a-a quote here from Dr. Picot
对无国界医生组织说的
to Medecins Sans Frontieres:
我给中南部的帮派成员和连环杀手
"I have operated on gang members in South Central
做了手术
and serial killers.
我要如何跟恐怖分子划清界限呢
How can I draw a line with terrorists?"
我明白了  助理联邦检察官是想
I see. So, the AUSA now wants to
因为我们当事人的思想而囚禁他
imprison our client for his thoughts,
-而不是因为他的行动  -我只是认为
- not his actions. - I just thought
法官阁下会喜欢这个上下文的语境
her Honor would enjoy a little context here.
我们当事人过去所说的话与本案毫无关联
Our client's past statements have no bearing on this case.
好了  好了
Okay. Okay.
我们不过在讨论审前保释  仅此而已
This is about a pretrial release, that's all.
不是最高法院  也不是海牙国际法庭
It's not the Supreme Court. It's not The Hague.
因此  我判决  被告缴纳两千美元假释金
Therefore, I rule: the defendant is ordered released
即可获得假释
on an unsecured bond of $2,000.
行政餐厅
An executive dining room.
我的天  你们手机塔的生意还真是好
My goodness, the cell tower business must be good.
你知道的  我们的合同都是你处理的
You should know, you're handling our contracts.
我们以前处理过
We were handling them.
今年好像有点耽误
There seems to be a holdup this year.
尝尝这个面包
Try this bread.
每天早晨现做的  我的办公室是就在楼上
They bake it every morning. My office is upstairs.
我整天都能闻到香味
I smell it all day.
说吧  罗恩
All right, come on, Ron,
什么情况  我们还没拿到律师费
what's going on? We haven't gotten our retainer.
我说了不算
It's not just up to me.
我们有董事会
I have a board.
每个人都有决策权
They all have a voice.
可我们签的是无招标合同  罗恩
But we're a no-bid contract, Ron.
我们提供服务所要缴纳的税款可减免两成
You get a tax credit for 20% of our work.
你是对我们的工作不满意吗
Are you unsatisfied with our work?
那是为什么
Then what?
事情有变化
Things have changed.
什么意思
What does that mean?
非得我一五一十说清楚吗
Do I really have to spell it out?
我觉得需要
I think you do.
新的政府
A new administration.
-新的总统  -但他们不会取消
- A new president. - But they're not pulling back
和少数族裔企业做生意而得到的税费减免
on tax credits for hiring minority-owned businesses.
对啊  但是你们并不是唯一的少数族裔企业
Yes, but you are not the only minority-owned business.
那我们说的是哪家呢
So who else are you talking to?
四点钟的时候回来
Look, come back in at 4:00.
跟董事会谈谈
Talk to the board.
亮出你们的底牌
Explain your bid.
我相信他们会听进去的
I'm sure they'll listen.
好的
Okay.
你们先走吧
Go ahead,
我坐下一趟
I'll take the next one.
是因为我反对特朗普的言论
It's what I said against Trump.
我在一次集会上说的
I spoke at a rally.
不  许多人都反对特朗普
Mm, no, a lot of folks spoke out against Trump. It's...
那是因为什么
Then what?
说啊
What?
因为安德鲁·哈特
It's Andrew Hart.
我以为他早就关门大吉了
I thought he went out of business.
他开了一家12人的律所  在黄金海岸那边
He runs a 12-man operation - on the Gold Coast.
12人  他开什么玩笑
12 men? Is he fucking kidding?
我们有80名律师呢
We have 80 lawyers here.
是少数族裔企业吗
It's minority-owned?
是的  他们刚从华盛顿特区搬到这来
Yes. They just moved here from D.C.
那就是因为他们的政府背景关系了
So it's about their government connections?
要我猜的话
My guess?
不止这些
Something more.
比如呢
Like what?
安德鲁·哈特是少数的参与特朗普竞选的
Andrew Hart is one of the few African-American businessmen
美国黑人商人
who ran a Trump PAC.
所以我们就要因为没有迎合特朗普而破产了
So we're going bankrupt 'cause we didn't pander to Trump.
他的脉搏很微弱  医生
His pulse is weaker, doctor.
他的发烧已经控制住了
His fever has spiked.
我们给他静脉注射了
We gave him I.V. Fluids,
但是他的血压还是不停地降
but his blood pressure is falling anyway.
没关系的  尤瑟夫
Okay, it's okay, Yusuf.
告诉他给病人加大静脉注射
Tell him to give the patient more I.V. Fluid.
他必须要把切口重新打开
He's gonna have to reopen the incision.
会有些肿
It will be swollen.
好吧  等下  我要翻译一下
O-Okay, hold on. I need to translate.
等等   尤瑟夫
Wait, h-hold on, Yusuf,
照我说的做  完后打给我
call me back when you've done all that.
为什么
Why?
我不知道他们是怎么窃听到上次的视频电话
I don't know how they tapped the last Skype.
我得找个更安全的地方
I need to get to a more secure place.
-一会打给你  -等下  什么...
- I'll call you back. - Wait, what...
尤瑟夫  你在吗
Yusuf, are you there?
在  你在哪
Yes, where are you?
我在外面
I'm outside.
我可能会走动
I might be moving.
进行到哪一步了
Where are we?
病人已插管  胸腔打开了  医生
The patient is intubated and the chest is open, doctor.
现在怎么办
Now what should he do?
确保没有再出血
Uh... make sure there's no new bleeding.
可能心脏上有个我们没发现的伤口
Could be a laceration in the heart that we missed.
好吧  我们要非常小心  动作要慢
Okay, we're gonna take this nice and slowly.
医生
Doctor?
-等一下  -医生
- Yeah, one second. - Doctor.
好了  告诉他放下引流管
Okay, tell him to leave the drain,
用抗生素清洗心脏周围然后缝合
wash around the heart with antibiotics and close up.
没有时间了
There isn't much time.
打给别人  他还有六个小时
Call somebody else. He has six hours.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的话都将成为呈堂...
Anything you say can and will be used against you...
你最近怎么样  爸
How've you been, dad?
抱歉  玛娅现在需要律师在场
Sorry, it's just important that Maia have her lawyer present.
好的
Yeah.
我很好  你呢
I'm good, and you?
你怎么样  玛娅
How are you, Maia?
就当我不存在
Just act like I'm not here.
我很好  也很好
I'm good. I'm good, too.
我们能有点私人空间吗  鲁珀特
Can we, uh, get a little space here, Rupert?
抱歉
Sorry.
作为你的律师  亨利  我不建议这样做
As your lawyer, Henry, I can't advise it.
我听说你找了个新工作
So I heard you got a new job.
是啊  挺好的  我很喜欢这份工作
Uh, yeah, yeah, it's good. I like it.
我知道你会的
Oh, I knew you would.
你妈告诉我你接了一个大案子
And Mom told me that you got a big case.
妈妈来过了吗
Mom was here?
是的  今早
This morning, yes.
我告诉了她你今天要来
I told her you'd be coming today.
她说了什么吗
Did she say anything?
什么事
About?
我不知道
I don't know.
-说了什么吗  -这个...
- Anything? - Well, uh,
就说你和艾米接到了骚扰电话
just that you and Amy are getting harassing calls.
还有你很喜欢新的律所
That you're enjoying this new law firm.
还有你很担心妈妈的癌症复发
And that you were worried about Mom's cancer scare.
提到贾克斯了吗
Anything about Jax?
我觉得我们不应该谈到这个话题
I really don't think we should go there.
没事  鲁珀特
It's okay, Rupert.
她就说他还在为这次庞氏骗局责怪我
Just that he still blames me for this Ponzi scheme.
-就这个吗  -是的
- That's it? - Yeah.
怎么了  还有什么
Why? What else?
你真...
Do you re...
你真的觉得妈妈在  帮助你吗
Do you really think that mom is... helping you?
帮我什么
Helping me with...?
她是支持你还是
Well, is she standing by you or,
还是她站在贾克斯这边
you know, is she standing by... Jax?
为什么你妈要站在贾克斯那边
Why would mom stand by Jax?
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
你就没有什么担心的事吗
But is that something that worries you?
你有什么需要担心的事吗
Do you have any reason to be worried?
我们不能再谈下去了
We should end this.
好吧
Okay.
贾克斯的个人电脑
Jax's personal computer.
-看门狗...  -亨利  不行
- Watchdog... - Henry, no.
我们  我们走  走吧
Let's... mm. Let's go, come on.
不  亨利  不行
No, Henry, no.
-亨利  不  -走  走  我们走
- Henry, no! - Come on, come on, let's go.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见  爸
Good-bye, dad.
再见  亲爱的
Good-bye, sweetheart.
玛娅  他说了什么
Maia, what did he say?
Maia, what?
没什么
Nothing.
他只说了  "我爱你"
He just said... "I love you."
得了吧
Oh, come on.
给我看看
All right, let me see.
不管他要你做什么  玛娅  你都不能做
Whatever he asked you to do, Maia, you can't do it.
你做的事不受保密特权保护
There's no privilege here.
配偶可以不出庭作证
A spouse can be prevented from testifying,
但你不行
but you can't.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们搞的好像已经没戏了
We're acting like this is over.
他们在和我们玩硬的
They're just playing a little hardball with us.
所以我们把要价降低百分之十
So we lower our bid by ten percent.
问题是他们依靠政府给他们的发射塔的
The problem is they rely on the government for low lease rates
低租赁利率
for their cell towers.
他们不想惹恼特朗普政府
They don't want to piss off the Trump administration.
和我们打交道怎么会惹恼特朗普政府
Why would they piss off the Trump administration with us?
因为我们是我们...
Because we're us...
还有你们
...you guys.
和那些警察暴力执法案件有关
Because of all the police brutality cases.
那我们怎么办
So what do we do?
谁给特朗普投了票
Who voted for Trump?
我们就从事前限制这点下手
We argue prior restraint.
他们说他不能实施手术
They're saying he can't operate,
即使他们没有证明...
even before they prove...
我们不必如此
We don't have to go there.
他们还没提供任何能证明病人身份的证据
They haven't presented evidence on the patient's identity yet.
那我们就得做两手准备
Okay, then we should argue both.
卢卡  你只是次席律师
Lucca, you're second chair.
是没错  但我知道怎么对付这家伙
Yes, but I know how to go after this guy.
他不是问题关键  关键是法律
He is not the problem; the problem is the law.
两者皆是
It's both.
好吧  你先上
Okay, you go first.
为什么
Why?
你能分散他的注意力
You distract him.
皮科医生试图对同一个恐怖分子指导二次手术
Dr. Picot attempted a second operation on the same terrorist.
-逮捕他属于事前限制  -非得这样吗
- Arresting him again is prior restraint. - Seriously?
我能把话说完吗  法官阁下
May I finish, Your Honor?
你俩互相认识吗
Do you two know each other?
法官阁下  被告已不能以不知情做为辩护点了
Your Honor, the defendant can no longer argue ignorance.
他现在知道该病人就是恐怖分子
He knows the patient is a terrorist now.
他怎么知道的
How does he know that?
-是啊  怎么知道的  -奎因女士
- Yeah, how? - Ms. Quinn.
因为三小时前
He knows because he was here
我们就此事辩论时他在场
three hours ago when we argued he was a terrorist.
但有何依据呢  我们没看到任何证据
But with what evidence? We didn't hear any evidence.
-证据属于机密  -还真是个好理由
- That evidence is confidential. - And here we go.
不幸的是国家的敌人依旧存在
Yes, unfortunately, this country still has enemies.
所以抱歉造成你的不便了  奎因女士
Sorry to inconvenience you, Ms. Quinn.
他才19岁
He's 19 years old.
不可能是恐怖分子
He's not a terrorist.
一处巴格达市场就是被一个15岁小子炸毁的
A Baghdad market was just blown up by a 15-year-old.
恐怖主义可不分年龄大小  先生
Terrorism doesn't honor age, sir.
皮科医生  这个在叙利亚的年轻人还能撑多久
Dr. Picot, how long does this young man in Syria have to live?
四个小时
Four hours.
那我得在五点前结束这个案子
So I have until 5:00 to decide this case.
那好
All right, then.
我要听取是否批准皮科医生保释的证据
I will hear evidence on Dr. Picot's pretrial release.
您已经准许他保释了
You have already granted his release.
法官阁下  这次手术不能进行
Your Honor, this operation cannot happen.
停  停  停
No, no, no, no, no, no.
你们只有三个半小时来展示证据
You have three and a half hours to present evidence.
所以别再吵了  直接上证据
Stop arguing and get me the evidence.
联邦法庭
梅丽莎  有个紧急情况
Marissa, it's an emergency.
我需要一名医师资格委员会成员出庭作证
I need a witness from the Medical Licensing Board right now.
好  你需要这位证人做什么准备
Yeah, where do you want him or her, this witness?
行不用说了  我马上办
Okay, I'm on it, I'm on it.
你在找什么
W-What do you need?
调查员
The investigator.
我不知道是谁
Oh, I don't know who that is.
他大概有这么高  黑人
He's about this tall, black.
这等于白说对吧
That's not very helpful, is it?
那什么  我叫梅丽莎
I'm Marissa, by the way.
-玛娅  -我的座位在那边
- Maia. - I work over there.
我知道  很高兴认识你
No, I know. Nice to meet you.
我给戴安干活  不过她不在的时候
I work for Diane, but when she's out,
如果你有需要可以随时找我
tell me if you need anything.
下午四点你有事吗
What are you doing at 4:00?
你给他投了票也没关系
It's okay if you voted for him.
我们只是需要一个人去竞标
We just need someone for a bid.
不好意思  打扰一下
Sorry, sorry, hi.
能借一步说话吗
Do you have a minute?
怎么了
Why?
你说让我碰到
You wanted me to tell you
需要调查的事情时就找你
when I was needed to do something investigative.
刚才正好来了件这样的事
I just was needed to do something investigative.
天哪  我们有80名律师和50名职工
Wow, we have 80 lawyers and 50 staff
居然连一个给特朗普投票的都没有
and not a single one voted for Trump?
或者说没有一个愿意承认的
Or not a single one wanted to admit it.
干脆我撒谎说我给他投了好了
Maybe I'll just lie, say I voted for him.
芭芭拉  你有空吗
Barbara, have you got a moment?
你想说什么
What's on your mind?
不会有任何影响的  对吧
There won't be any repercussions, right?
真的假的
Seriously?
完蛋了
Oh, my God.
等等  你...
Wait. You...
给特朗普投了票
voted for Trump?
很好
Good.
那代表人选就是你了
Then you will pitch for us.
我讨厌这个
Oh, I hate this.
我懂  但这是为了律所
I know, but it's for the firm.
那个  我...
Look, I, uh...
我不会被排挤的  对吧
I don't get ostracized, right?
我不会被孤立吧
I-I don't get isolated?
听着  坎耶也投给特朗普了
Look, Kanye voted for Trump.
坎耶：美国说唱歌手
不  他没有
No, he didn't.
他只说过如果投票的话他会投给他
He said he would've if he did vote.
对
Right.
除了我和阿德里安不会有其他人知道
Well, no one's gonna know but Adrian and myself.
真的吗
Really?
他有说原因吗
Did he say why?
因为他是保守派吧
Conservative politics.
好吧
Ah. Well,
坎耶也投给特朗普了
Kanye voted for Trump.
不  只是他如果真去投票的话  就会投他
No, he didn't, but he would have - if he had voted.
律所代言人找到了
We have our spokesperson.
听着
Listen,
我答应他  他在这儿不会遭到排挤
I promised him he would not be ostracized here.
那是当然
Of course not.
麦克  来个八盎司汉堡  多加洋葱
Mike, an eight ounce, extra onions.
我马上要去法院
I'm headed to court.
你还有多少时间
How much time you got?
十分钟
Ten minutes.
这时间太紧了
That's cutting it close.
吃吧  这半个给你
Here, have half.
不了  没事
No, I'm fine.
法官说三点开庭  你肯定来不及的
Judge said 3:00. You're not gonna make it in time.
他说的没错  我需要12分钟来做汉堡
He's right. I need 12 minutes.
吃吧
Go ahead.
我喜欢多加洋葱和胡椒
I like extra onions, peppers.
如你所需
Done.
你要输了
You're losing.
这案子我稳操胜券
This one's a slam dunk.
很好
Good.
我就喜欢帮助男人解决他们自视甚高的问题
I like helping men with their self-esteem issues.
是位好律师吗
Good lawyer?
很有天赋
Very talented.
那笑容能让你走多远呢
So how far does a smile get you?
那个
The...
那个坏小子汤姆·克鲁斯式的笑容
The bad boy Tom Cruise smiles.
法官会为之疯狂吗
Do the judges go wild for it?
靠那个还有优秀的庭上辩论
That and a good argument.
不
No.
我觉得你一直在依靠你那点都市型男魅力
I think you've always relied on the cute little metrosexual thing.
那种"天呐  从事法律只是我误打误撞"的
The, "Oh, my God, the law is just something I stumbled into,"
傻笑
shit-eating grin.
真是敏锐的感知力
Wow, the powers of perception.
谢谢
Thanks.
不管谁赢了都要请对方喝一杯
Whoever wins buys the other a drink.
你难道
Won't you be busy...
不用跟你那位金发小律师忙点什么吗
with your good blonde lawyer there?
我可以挤出时间来
Oh, I'll make time.
让我考虑一下
Let me think about it.
谢谢你的汉堡
Thanks for the burger.
这是在小题大做  法官阁下
This is melodrama, Your Honor.
为什么是小题大做
Why is it melodrama?
如果这个男人得不到他所需的医疗救助
If this man does not get the help he needs,
他会死的
he will die.
-我的上帝啊  -可以称得上谋杀了
- Oh, my God. - That is an assassination attempt!
我们是在阻止他医治一位恐怖分子
We're preventing him from making a terrorist well.
仅此而已  这是一位
That's all. This is a terrorist
可能会导致成千上万人死亡的恐怖分子
who could be responsible for the death of thousands.
法官阁下  我们有一位证人要出庭作证
Your Honor, we have a witness.
感谢上帝  快让她赶紧宣誓上庭
Thank God. Let's swear someone in, please.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
其实  不是我的功劳  是
Actually, it wasn't me, it was...
好吧
Okay.
我叫玛拉·库尔卡尼
Mala Kulkarni.
我是伊利诺伊州医师资格委员会的主席
I am president of the Medical Licensing Board of Illinois.
你能告诉我们这是什么吗
And can you tell the court what this is?
这是伊利诺伊州法律汇编中
It is the section of the Illinois Compiled Statutes
关于医生违纪处分的章节
that deals with disciplinary actions against doctors.
在吊销行医执照的处罚理由列表中
And under the list of grounds for revoking a medical license,
你能读一下第16条吗
could you read number 16?
"放弃病人"
"Abandonment of a patient."
能解释下是什么意思吗
And what does that mean?
一旦一位医生同意去医治一位病人
Once a doctor has agreed to care for a patient,
他或者她就必须负责到底
he or she must follow through,
除非他能找到一位适格的替代者
unless he can find an adequate substitute.
如果他不能做到这一点呢
And if he doesn't?
他会失去他的行医执照
He loses his license.
法官阁下  控方正把皮科医生
Your Honor, the State is putting Dr. Picot
置于一个进退两难的境地
in an untenable position.
如果他不许进行这台手术
If he doesn't continue this operation,
他会失去他的行医执照
he will lose his license.
我们有一位反驳证人  法官阁下
We have a rebuttal witness, Your Honor.
我是斯宾塞·玛拉上校
Colonel Spencer Mara.
我管理华盛顿州路易斯麦科得联合基地的
I command Madigan Army Medical Center,
麦迪根陆军医疗中心
out of Lewis-McChord, Washington.
玛拉医生  你对战斗中医治伤员的情况
Dr. Mara, are you familiar with treating patients
-熟悉吗  -很熟悉
- during combat conditions? - I am.
一旦你接手一位病人
And once you start treating a patient,
你总能负责到底吗
do you always stay with them until the end?
当然会尽量
You try, obviously.
但有时候这么做并不安全
But sometimes it's not safe.
有时候别的地方需求更高
Sometimes you are needed somewhere else urgently.
你不会因此失去行医执照  对吗
You wouldn't expect to lose your license over it, would you?
不会  考虑到战场的特殊情况
No. Not given battlefield conditions.
我问完了
Your witness.
你应该知道  玛拉医生
Uh, you're aware, Dr. Mara,
日内瓦公约要求为敌方作战人员
that the Geneva Convention requires the proper care
提供适当的照顾和治疗对吗
and treatment of enemy fighters?
我知道
I am aware.
根据那些条款  皮科医生难道不会被要求
By those rules, wouldn't Dr. Picot be required
-去医治他的病人吗  -日内瓦公约
- to treat his patient? - The Geneva Convention
只适用于国与国之间武装冲突的情况
only applies to cases involving enemy conflict between states.
我问的不是这个问题
That's not my question.
反对  法官阁下
Uh, objection, Your Honor.
证人应该被允许自由回答问题
The witness should be allowed to answer.
同意  请继续
Agreed. Go ahead.
现在这个情况并不属于国与国之间的武装冲突
This is not an armed conflict between states.
这位病人是一位伊斯兰国战士
The patient is an ISIS fighter
因此他是一位敌方作战人员
and therefore he is an enemy combatant.
了解了
I see.
所以问题出在这位病人是伊斯兰国战士上吗
So this is different because the patient is an ISIS fighter?
没错
Exactly.
你的意思是不是  玛拉医生
Don't you mean by that, Dr. Mara...
我觉得医生可以表达自己的意思  律师
I think the doctor can speak for himself, Counselor.
你是如何得知这位病人是一位伊斯兰国战士的
How do you know the patient is an ISIS fighter?
医生
Doctor?
我  我可能是口误了
I... I may have misspoke.
但是你知道患者是伊斯兰国战士
But you know the patient is an ISIS fighter?
请回答问题  医生
Doctor, answer the question.
是的
I do.
那你怎么知道他是伊斯兰国战士的
And how do you know the patient is an ISIS fighter?
助理联邦检察官说的
From the AUSA.
法官阁下
Your Honor,
政府的证人刚刚
the government's witness
揭露了病人的身份
just opened the door to the patient's identity.
伊斯兰国只是一个概称  法官阁下
ISIS is a generic term, Your Honor.
不是的  且控方证人刚刚也
No, it is not. And the prosecution's witness
争辩说他是伊斯兰国成员
has just argued that he's a member of ISIS.
我们需要弄清楚他是怎么知道的
We need to be shown how he knows this.
她说得没错  助理联邦检察官先生
She got you there, Mr. AUSA.
信息得共享了  他是谁
The kimono is opened. Who is he?
我们需要几小时去收集这些信息
we'll-we'll need a few hours to gather this information.
不行不行
No, no, no.
皮科医生的患者两小时后就要死了  他是谁
Dr. Picot's patient will be dead in two hours. Who is he?
他是塔里克.阿布拉菲亚
He is Tariq Aboulafia.
谢谢  是叙利亚公民吗
Thank you. A citizen of Syria?
不
No.
是美国公民
The United States.
我还在想你会不会来
I was wondering if you'd ever come by.
我这不就来了
Here I am.
你上次来是什么时候
When was the last time you were here?
圣诞节
Uh, Christmas.
对  点了巧克力糖衣草莓
Oh, that's right. Chocolate-covered strawberries.
要点什么呢  玛娅
What can I get you, Maia?
答案
Answers.
我想的是啤酒之类的
Well, I was thinking more a beer,
不过要答案也可以
but I could probably manage a few of those, too.
你爸爸怎么说
What'd your dad say?
庞氏骗局责任在你
You're responsible for the Ponzi scheme.
他发现了  因此你才去联调局嫁祸他
He caught you, that's why you went to the feds and blamed him.
而他和丽诺只是无辜受害者
And he and Lenore were just unsuspecting victims...
这怎么不会是真相呢
How's that not the truth?
你知道真相的  玛娅
You know the truth, Maia.
这些年你一直看着你父母的作为
You watched your parents all those years.
你爸爸想要做别人眼中的金融天才
Your dad wanted to be seen as some genius of finance.
「财富」杂志的那些文章
Those articles in Fortune?
那些不是我要的  是他
I never wanted them, he did.
他最不想承认的事情就是所有成就都是运气
The last thing he wanted to admit was it was all luck.
他在股票投资上并无天分
He was no genius at stocks.
你扔个飞镖中靶概率估计都比他的投资好
You throw a dart at a board, it'd be more accurate.
所以当泡沫破裂的时候
So when the bubble hit,
他仍旧对外宣传他还在获利
he kept sending out statements that he was still winning.
这才是关于你爸爸的真相
That's the real truth about your dad.
他不是想诈骗别人的钱财
He didn't want to steal people's money.
他只是想被看作成功者
He just wanted to be seen as a winner.
你为什么要和我妈搞在一起
Why are you sleeping with my mom?
我没有
I'm not sleeping with your mom.
你去死吧
Fuck you.
去接电话吧  我不会跑的
Go ahead. I'm not going anywhere.
喂  嗨
Yeah? Hey.
看门狗2849
没  我现在有点忙
No, I'm a little busy right now.
不是不是
No, no.
好的
Okay.
贾克斯·林德尔
林德尔基金
我不是很明白  究竟是什么事
No, I don't understand. What is this regarding?
很重要的事情有关  跟你的案件有关
It's regarding a very important matter regarding your suit.
抱歉我说了两次"有关"
Sorry for saying "Regarding" twice.
我的案件  你把我搞糊涂了
Uh, my suit? I'm confused.
关于林德尔案  戴安·洛哈特有很重要的
Diane Lockhart has some important information for you
信息给你
regarding the Rindell matter.
我的律师不是她
She's not my lawyer.
我知道  但是她有信息提供给你
I know, but she has information for you.
好
Okay.
-能让她听电话吗  -只要一小会儿
- Can you put her on? - Actually, just one second.
首先  我需要你写下关于戴安的信息
First, I need you to write something down regarding Diane.
有笔吗
Do you have a pen?
好
okay.
因为事关重大
This is very important.
请你真真确确地记下
Please write it down exactly.
号码  八 七 三 一 零 九
The numbers 8, 7, 3, 1, 0, 9,
小写的H
lowercase "H",
大写的R  大写的
capital letter "R", Capital letter...
林德尔基金  鬼混名单
大写的U
Capital letter "U".
然后是号码九和三  你重复一遍吧
Then the numbers 9 and 3. Why don't you repeat it back?
你刚刚说这是什么事
What is this about again?
戴安和你说话前要你记下暗号
Diane wanted you to have this code before you two talked.
-为什么  -我  什么为什么
-  Why? - I, um, why?
事情来去始末没人告诉我
I wasn't told all the whys and wherefores,
但是我感觉挺重要的
but it seemed very important.
等下  你到底要什么
One second. What do you need?
-你  -我  干什么
- You. - Me? Why?
我们搞到叙利亚那病人的名字了
We got the name of the patient in Syria.
他家人住在芝加哥  没人愿意和我聊
His family lives in Chicago and they won't talk to me.
他们为什么不愿意和你说话
Why won't they talk to you?
等我一下
Okay, one second.
戴安需要你等一下
Diane needs you to hold a second,
她想和你说话
and she wants to talk to you.
告诉她等会儿再打过来  我有客人在
Tell her to call me back. I have a guest here.
不  等等  她来了  戴安  接通他了
No, wait, wait, here she is. Diane, he's on right now.
不  说真的  他在等你接电话  他有客人
No, seriously, he's on the phone. He has a guest.
他有点不耐烦了
He's getting impatient.
好的  我会告诉他的
Okay, I'll tell him.
她被联邦调查局耽搁了
She's just hanging up with the feds
他们有重要消息要告诉你
and they have important information for you.
我要挂电话了
I'm hanging up now.
不  我要挂电话了
No, I'm hanging up.
让她给我回电话  不
Tell her to call me back. No.
那我很抱歉  再见
Then I'm sorry. Good-bye.
抱歉
Sorry.
那是谁
Who was that?
-戴安的助理  -哦
- Diane's assistant. - Oh.
我们刚刚说到哪里了
Where were we?
我得走了
I have to go.
你说你给他投票了
You mention that you voted for him.
我不要只去说"我给特朗普投票了"
I am not just gonna say "I voted for Trump."
为什么不
Why not?
因为我不是能因此被定义的
Because I am not defined by that.
那就说说我们律所能代表多样化观点的理由
Then say why our firm represents a cross section of opinions.
特朗普和希拉里的支持率是1比98
Uh, yeah. One Trump supporter, 98 Hillary supporters.
这事你不知道
You don't know that.
朱利叶斯
Hey, Julius.
你给特朗普提供资金了吗
Did you actually give Trump money?
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
你店里的东西很漂亮
Beautiful stuff you have here.
谢谢  你需要点什么
Thank you. What are you looking for?
我需要你  你有空吗
You, I guess. Do you have a minute?
你和他是一起的吗
Are you with him?
不是
No.
是的
Yes.
这事跟你儿子有关
This is about your son.
塔里克在叙利亚  他需要你的帮助
Tariq is in Syria, and he needs your help.
这是我儿子塔里克  他不是恐怖分子
This is my son, Tariq. He is not a terrorist.
法官阁下  这是病人的妈妈
Your Honor, this is the patient's mother...
可以让我们说完吗
May we finish?
可以
Yes, you may.
莫雷洛先生  会轮到你发言的
Mr. Morrello, you'll have your moment.
你儿子为什么会在叙利亚
Why was your son, Tariq, in Syria?
他  他想劝他哥哥回家
He... he wanted to convince his brother to come home.
他哥哥  他哥哥叫什么
His brother. And what is the name of his brother?
艾马尔
Aimar.
是艾马尔·阿布拉菲亚吗
And this would be Aimar Aboulafia,
那个美国通缉要犯名单中的恐怖分子
a terrorist on America's Most Wanted list?
所以  塔里克的哥哥  艾马尔
So Tariq's brother, Aimar,
才是美国正在通缉的恐怖分子
would seem to be the terrorist the U.S. is after,
而不是塔里克
not Tariq?
塔里克飞往叙利亚去阻止他
Tariq flew to Syria to try to stop him.
他不是恐怖分子
He is not a terrorist.
他是个学生  学化学专业
He is a student here. He is studying chemistry.
他是带着机票飞往叙利亚的吗
And he flew to Syria with an airline ticket?
是的  为了把艾马尔带回家
Yes! To bring him home.
法官阁下  您应该允许皮科医生
Your Honor, Dr. Picot should be allowed
继续给塔里克手术  因为他救的人
to continue Tariq's surgery because the person he is helping
不仅不是恐怖分子
not only is not a terrorist,
而且还在劝说一个恐怖分子回家
he is trying to persuade a terrorist to come home.
莫雷洛先生  有什么事吗
Mr. Morrello. Anything?
是的  法官阁下  请稍等
Yes, Your Honor. One second, please.
「美国法典」第2339A条禁止任何人
U.S. Code 2339A prohibits anyone from knowingly
有意为恐怖分子或恐怖组织
providing material support of any kind
提供任何形式的实质帮助
to a terrorist or terrorist organization.
不幸的是  根据阿布拉菲亚夫人的供述
Unfortunately, by Ms. Aboulafia's admission,
塔里克恰恰做了这样的事
that is exactly what Tariq did.
-什么  法官阁下  -法官阁下
- What? Your Honor... - Your Honor.
这垂死挣扎真让我大开眼界
This is a new level of desperation.
你说的实质帮助是什么呢
What material support are we talking about here?
机票
The airplane tickets.
他想把他哥哥带回家
He wanted to bring his brother home.
没错  这就是提供了实质帮助
Yes, which is supplying material support.
上帝啊  这真是令人惊叹的诡辩
Oh, my God, the sophistry here is amazing.
法官阁下
Your Honor,
第2339A条的规定是意图中立的
Code 2339A is content neutral.
事实上  最高法院在
In fact, the Supreme Court decision
霍尔德诉人道主义法计划案的判决中
in Holder v. Humanitarian Law Project made it very clear
明确表示在人道主义法计划中
that the good intentions of the Law Project
善意动机并不能否定其行为的有罪性
made no difference as to their culpability.
重要的是实质帮助本身
All that mattered is the material support itself.
这些机票明显是实质帮助
These airline tickets are clearly material support.
很可惜  我认同
Unfortunately, I agree.
-法官阁下  -这不是
- Your Honor. - This is not...
不
No, no.
在精神上我站在你这一边
I may agree with you on the spirit,
但在法律意义上则不然
but not the letter of the law.
霍尔德诉人道主义法计划案是最高法院判例
Holder v. HLP is a Supreme Court precedent,
本法庭必须遵守其判决
and that is how this court rules,
不论我的裁决对那叙利亚的可怜人意味着什么
despite what my verdict means for the poor man in Syria.
被告应被拘留直至审判开始
The defendant is hereby detained until trial.
是的  我们需要皮科医生
Y-Yes, we need Dr. Picot.
不幸的是  他被羁留了  尤瑟夫
Unfortunately, he's being held, Yusuf.
病人情况不太好
The patient is not doing well.
我知道  我们还在研究策略
I know, we're still working on options.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
有个人
There is someone here.
他在威胁医护人员
He is threatening the staff.
怎么威胁的
Threatening with what?
如果我们不做手术  他就会杀人
Unless we operate, he will kill someone.
尤瑟夫  你能把手机朝向他吗
Uh, Yusuf, can you turn the iPhone toward him?
那个威胁人的人
The threatening man?
-为什么  -拜托了  把手机朝向他
- Why? - Please. Can you turn the iPhone?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这个男人
That man right there.
是病人的哥哥  艾马尔
That's the patient's brother, Aimar.
他在威胁医护人员
He's threatening the medical staff.
如果病人死了  他会杀了他们
If the patient dies, he will kill them.
法官阁下  法庭必须考虑到损害衡量
Your Honor, this court must consider the balance of hardships.
塔里克·阿布拉菲亚给一个生命垂危的
The risk of Tariq Aboulafia giving a plane ticket
恐怖分子飞机票属于长远的低风险
to a terrorist are low and distant.
而整个医疗团队被一名情绪激动的
The risk of an entire medical staff being slaughtered
恐怖分子所残杀属于迫切的高风险
by a terrorist are high and immediate.
而损害衡量要求
The balance of the hardships demand
手术必须继续进行
that this surgery proceed.
莫雷洛先生  还有什么要说的吗
Mr. Morrello, anything?
干得漂亮
Good job.
你也是
You, too.
不  不  别谢我
No, no, no. Don't thank me.
谢他  朱利叶斯这个好说客
Thank Ju... Julius pitched.
朱利叶斯  好说客
Julius pitched!
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
你没有给特朗普投票
You didn't vote for Trump.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你没有给特朗普投票
You didn't vote for Trump.
你赢了竞标  但谎言够好就能战无不胜
You won the bid, but you can win anything if you lie enough.
这并不重要  但我没撒谎
Uh, not that it matters, but I didn't lie.
那你这一生将注定孤独  朋友
Then you are in for a very lonely life, my friend.
好吧
Yeah.
我挺忙的  朋友  所以...
I'm a little busy, my friend. So, uh...
他们会因你帮他们赢了竞标感谢你
They'll thank you for winning the bid for them.
会跟你握手
They'll shake your hand.
会赞赏地拍你后背
They'll slap you on the back.
会鼓掌
They'll applaud.
但也仅此而已
And that will be it.
你走过长长的路回到这间办公室
You'll take the long walk back to this office.
人们却不会再来拜访
And people will stop coming by.
他们不再需要你的帮助
They'll stop needing your help.
好吧  谢谢  再见
Okay, thank you. Good-bye.
如果这种事真的发生了...
For the day when that happens...
哈特&斯蒂芬斯律师事务所
安德鲁·哈特
高级合伙人
干得漂亮
Good job.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么
What?
你以为你是我喜欢的型
You think you're my type.
并不是
You're not.
为什么不是
Hmm. Why am I not?
你太过滑头
You're too slick.
你看你
I mean, look at you.
那头发
The hair.
那发胶
The gel.
那不是发胶  我头发干了就这样
Oh, that's not gel. My hair just settles that way.
我帮你个忙
Look, I'm gonna do you a favor.
我帮你从酒吧里选个人  好吗
I'll choose someone for you from the bar. Okay?
合适的人
Someone appropriate.
那赶紧开始吧
I can't wait.
选谁
Who do we got?
不是他  他有点...
Not him. He's a...
-我还挺喜欢他的  -不
- Oh, I quite like him, actually. - Uh, oh.
-真可爱  - 那里
- Adorable. - There.
中间那个
In the middle.
-不错  -没错
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
金发的
The blonde.
是挺不错的
I'm not mad at that.
嗯
Yeah.
她很完美
She's perfect.
你去哪里
Where you going?
回家
Home.
等我一下
Give me one second.
什么事
Yeah.
实时新闻  美国在叙利亚危机中取得重大胜利
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
什么时候
When?
麦克  能把声音开大点吗
Michael? Can you turn that up?
为什么没人告诉我
Why wasn't I told?
由美国领导的联合军事行动取得重大胜利
In a major victory for U.S. led coalition forces,
空袭击杀了艾马尔·阿布拉菲亚
the airstrike killed Aimar Aboulafia,
他是伊斯兰国的美籍领袖
an American-born leader of the Islamic State.
艾马尔·阿布拉菲亚被击杀
据叙利亚地面救援组织
According to the White Helmets,
「白头盔」介绍
first responders on the ground in Syria,
空袭还击杀了...
the airstrike also killed...
我之前不知道
I didn't know.
不知道什么
Didn't know what?
阿布拉菲亚在芝加哥长大
Aboulafia was raised in Chicago,
实时新闻  美国在叙利亚危机中取得重大胜利
与在伊拉克和叙利亚的恐怖活动都有关
and was linked to terrorist activity in Iraq, as well as Syria.
他们就想在法庭拖延时间
They wanted the delay in court.
我也被利用了
I was used, too.
跟你一样
Just like you.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他们就想把他哥哥引出来
They wanted to draw the brother out.
想让他去诊所
They wanted to get him to that clinic.
有消息称  同样死于空袭的还有
Also reportedly killed in the drone strike
伤亡人数共计34人  死者中包括美国公民
阿布拉菲亚的弟弟及34名医护人员
were Aboulafia's brother and 34 hospital personnel.
-你做到了  -嗯
- Oh... You did it. - Yeah.
是什么
What is it?
能毁了贾克斯的东西
Something to destroy Jax.
那妈妈呢
And Mom?
我不知道
I don't know.